A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller personal papers, Possessions, Series K FA011
Rockefeller Archive Center
Nelson A. Rockefeller personal papers, Possessions, Series K
1909-1976
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller, Nelson A. (Nelson Aldrich) (1908-1979)
FA011
25.84 Cubic Feet 68 letter document boxes
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC. Material in the Rockefeller family collections that provides the names, correspondence, or activities of living members of the Rockefeller family, and/or documents the net wealth of any Rockefeller family members, is restricted from access. Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) or audiovisual material (audio cassettes, VHS, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
Scope and Contents
This series comprises files about broad categories of items owned by Nelson A. Rockefeller, ranging from his automobiles and boats to his porcelains and honorary degrees. Researchers interested in his china, porcelain, and glass collections will also want to review Series C of his personal papers, which relates to his art collection.
Additionally, there are 10 boxes containing documentation on his real estate holdings in New York City, as well as general information regarding the Rockefeller family estate in Pocantico Hills, New York. Of special significance among the real estate files are 4 boxes on his Fifth Avenue apartment that date from 1934 to 1974. The earliest of this material includes correspondence about the interior design and furnishings by Parisian interior architect Jean-Michel Frank and Swiss sculptors Alberto and Diego Giacometti.
There is also information on the offices Nelson Rockefeller established on the property he already owned at 22 West 55th Street in Manhattan, which served as the New York City Office of the Governor. He maintained this office during his 15-year tenure as Governor of New York, becoming one of the first governors to have a permanent office in New York City in addition to the executive chamber in the New York State Capitol in Albany.
The folders in Box 12 regarding photographs are correspondence and billing information about specific photographic shoots or storage. Actual photographs of Nelson Rockefeller can be found in the associated NAR photograph collection.
Arrangement
Arranged alphabetically by subject matter.
Art, Modern
- Nelson A. Rockefeller Vouchers, 1934-1958; F.2
  - Furnishings, 2.1
    - Abco Steel, Inc. - Ar., 1949 September-1958 October (Box 1, Folder 1)
      Scope and Contents
      Furniture purchases for office or personal use for - 1. 13 West 54th Street, NYC. 2. 30 Rockefeller Plaza (51st Floor). 3. Pocantico Hills, Tarrytown, NY. 4. 810 Fifth Avenue, NYC. 5. Seal Harbor Home, Maine. 6. 2500 Foxhall Road, Washington, DC
    - Arthur Television - W. E. Clark, 1939 July-1955 March (Box 1, Folder 2)
      Furniture purchases for office or personal use for - A. Pocantico Hills (Guest House), Tarrytown, NY. B. Rockefeller Plaza (51st Floor). C. 2500 Foxhall Road, Washington, DC. D. 55th Street Garage, NYC. E. 810 Fifth Avenue, NYC. F. House, Seal Harbor, ME. G. House in Venezuela. H. Art Gallery, Seal Harbor, ME. I. NYO Film Library, NY
    - C - D, 1953 July-1956 May (Box 1, Folder 3)
      Furniture purchases for office or personal use for - A. 2500 Foxhall Road, Washington, DC. B. Health Education and Welfare Dept. C. 22 West 55th Street, NYC. D. NY Office, 56th Floor. E. 13 West 54th Street, NYC. F. Rockefeller Plaza, Room 5112.
    - C - D, 1952 June-1958 September (Box 1, Folder 4)
      Furniture purchases for office or personal use for - 13 West 54th Street, NYC. 30 Rockefeller Plaza (51st and 56th Floors). 810 Fifth Avenue, NYC. 22 West 55th Street, NYC. Pocantico Hills, NY. Art Gallery, Seal Harbor, ME. 2500 Foxhall Road, Washington DC.
    - Dauber, Carl W. & Sons - Furniture Mercantile Service, Inc., 1936 May-1958 October (Box 1, Folder 5)
      Furniture purchases for office or personal use for - 13 West 54th Street, NYC. 810 Fifth Avenue, NYC. 20 and 22 West 55th Street, NYC. Pocantico Hills, NY. Art Gallery, Seal Harbor, ME. 2500 Foxhall Road, Washington DC.
    - Grammer, Joseph - Grump's, 1934 December-1958 October (Box 1, Folder 6)
      Furniture purchases for office or personal use for - 13 West 54th Street, NYC. 30 Rockefeller Plaza (51st and 56th Floors). 810 Fifth Avenue, NYC. Seal Harbor, ME. 2500 Foxhall Road, Washington DC.
    - Hafner, Mark - Ilkin Brothers, Inc., 1935 January-1956 May (Box 1, Folder 7)
      Furniture purchases for office or personal use for - 13 West 54th Street, NYC. 30 Rockefeller Plaza (51st Floor). 810 Fifth Avenue, NYC. Pocantico Hills, NY. Seal Harbor, ME. 2500 Foxhall Road, Washington DC.
    - Ilkin Brothers, Inc., 1954 December-1958 October (Box 2, Folder 8)
      Furniture purchases for office or personal use for - 13 West 54th Street, NYC. 30 Rockefeller Plaza (51st Floor and Room 4329). DHEW, Washington DC. 22 West 55th Street and 20 West 55th Street, NYC.
    - Jackson, Wm. H. Co. - Kobelbauer, Joe, 1952 September-1958 December (Box 2, Folder 9)
      Furniture purchases for office or personal use for - 13 West 54th Street, NYC. Venezuela House. Pocantico Hills, NY. 810 Fifth Avenue, NYC. Seal Harbor Home, ME. 2500 Foxhall Road, Washington DC.
    - Langenbacher, John, Inc. - Loosen & Brautigam, 1935 January-1958 November (Box 2, Folder 10)
      Furniture purchases for office or personal use for - 1. Art Gallery, Seal Harbor, ME. 2. 2500 Foxhall Road, Washington DC. 3. 810 Fifth Avenue, NYC. 4. Seal Harbor Home, ME. 5. 13 West 54th Street, NYC.
    - Lord and Taylor - Mauretania Fabrics, Inc., 1936 September-1958 September (Box 2, Folder 11)
      Furniture purchases for office or personal use for - Washington DC Office and Home. 810 Fifth Avenue, NYC. Pocantico Hills, NY. 13 West 54th Street, NYC. House in Venezuela. Art Gallery, Seal Harbor, ME
    - Maloney, Gwendolyn - McCagney, John, Inc., 1935 January-1958 September (Box 2, Folder 12)
      Furniture purchases for office or personal use for - 1. 810 Fifth Avenue, NYC. 2. 13 West 54th Street, NYC. 3. 30 Rockefeller Plaza (51st Floor). 4. Seal Harbor, ME. 5. 20 and 22 West 55th Street, NYC.
    - McCutcheon's - Muller, Theodor Carl, 1937 September-1958 June (Box 2, Folder 13)
      Furniture purchases for office or personal use for - 1. House in Venezuela. 2. 810 Fifth Avenue, NYC. 3. Pocantico Hills (Guest House).
    - Muller, Barringer - Nichols, Marie, 1948 February-1958 October (Box 2, Folder 14)
      Furniture purchases for office or personal use for - 1. 810 Fifth Avenue, NYC. 2. House in Venezuela. 3. 13 West 54th Street, NYC. 4. Art Gallery, Seal Harbor, ME.
    - Ogden, Peter K. - Perkins, Edwin, 1935 November-1956 July (Box 3, Folder 15)
      Furniture purchases for office or personal use for - 810 Fifth Avenue, NYC. House in Venezuela. 13 West 54th Street, NYC. 30 Rockefeller Plaza, NYC. Pocantico Hills, NY.
    - Piazza - Rummler, Alfred, Inc., 1935 February-1957 May (Box 3, Folder 16)
      Furniture purchases for office or personal use for - 810 Fifth Avenue, NYC. 13 West 54th Street, NYC. 30 Rockefeller Plaza, NYC. Seal Harbor, ME.
    - Rummler, Alfred, Inc. - Saunders, R. J. Inc., 1949 September-1958 October (Box 3, Folder 17)
      Furniture purchases for office or personal use for - 1. 13 West 54th Street, NYC. 2. 30 Rockefeller Plaza. 3. House in Venezuela. 4. Pocantico Hills, Tarrytown, NY.
    - Schmidt, Elena B., 1934 November-1935 March (Box 3, Folder 18)
      Furniture purchases for office or personal use for - 810 Fifth Avenue, NYC.
    - Schmidt, Elena B. - Schorch, A. W., 1935 May-1945 July (Box 3, Folder 19)
      Furniture purchases for office or personal use for - 1. 810 Fifth Avenue, NYC. 2. 2500 Foxhall Road, Washington, DC.
    - Serota, S., Inc. - The Thermodyne Corp., 1935 January-1958 October (Box 3, Folder 20)
      Furniture purchases for office or personal use for - 1. Washington DC Office. 2. 2500 Foxhall Road, Washington DC. 3. House in Venezuela. 4. 13 West 54th Street, NYC. 5. 30 Rockefeller Plaza. 6. 810 Fifth Avenue, NYC. 7. Pocantico Hills, NY. 8. 55th Street Garage, NYC.
    - The Treasure House - Young, Edward L., 1936 May-1957 June (Box 3, Folder 21)
      Furniture purchases for office or personal use for - 1. Seal Harbor, ME. 2. Pocantico Hills, NY. 3. Washington DC Office. 2. 2500 Foxhall Road, Washington DC. 4. 810 Fifth Avenue, NYC. 5. 30 Rockefeller Plaza.
  - Boats, 2.2
    - Benjamin's for Motors - Jewett, A. G. (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Luders Marine Construction Co. - Manset Marine Supply Co. (Box 4, Folder 2)
      Purchases for the following boats - L-16 Sailboat Hull 834
    - Manset Marine Supply Co. - Mount Desert Yacht Yard, Inc. (Box 4, Folder 3)
      Purchases for the following boats - 1. Outboard motor (1955). 2. Johnson outboard motor (1957).
    - Peterson, Julius, Inc. - Nevins Yacht Yard (Box 4, Folder 4)
      Purchases for the following boats - Reynolds 12 foot aluminum boat
    - Stonington-Deer Isle Yacht Basin Corp. - Sparkman & Stephens (Box 4, Folder 5)
      Purchases for the following boats - Lengthening the "Dragon Lady" and services for the boat.
    - Sparkman & Stephens - Yarnell, Alex (Box 4, Folder 6)
      Purchases for the following boats - Designing services for the "Dragon Lady".
  - Machinery and Equipment, 2.3
    - R. Argento and Sons, Inc. - Eastern Fire Equipment (Box 4, Folder 1)
      Purchases such as: Vacuum leaf machine, lawn mower, Freezer, Beverage Cooler, engines, trailer, wheelbarrow, tractor, and the like.
    - Goldberg & Co. - West. Co. Grinding Shop (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Autos, 2.4
    - Chambers, Stephen - 55th Street Garage Fund (Box 5, Folder 1)
      Purchases of the following autos: 1. Austin (1950). 2. Chrysler Crown Imperial Limo (1956). 3. Convertible Coupe (1957). 4. Crosley Car (1941). 5. De Soto Limo (1938). 6. Lincoln Convertible Sedan (1938). 7. Crosley Sports Car (1949). 8. Ford Cabriolet (1936). 9. Lincoln Zephyr Convertible Coupe (1938).
    - Geilich Motor Co. - Jackson, Herbert H. (Box 5, Folder 2)
      Purchases of the following autos: 1. Dodge Pickup (1954). 2. Convertible Coupe (1938). 3. Jaguar, Mark V, Drophead Coupe (1949). 4. Jaguar, Mark VII (1951). 5. Ford Convertible Coupe (1948). 6. 1952 Ford pick-up Truck
    - Manhattan Auto - The Momo Co. (Box 5, Folder 3)
      Purchases of the following autos: 1. Austin Cambridge (1955). 2. Willys Station Wagon (1956). 3. De Soto Custom 7 passenger Limo (1941). 4. De Soto Custom Limo (1948). 5. De Soto Custom Limo (1950). 6. Buick Convertible Phaeton (1935). 7. Sperr Trailer (1946). 8. Pontiac (1953). 9. Chevrolet Station Wagon (1950). 10. Oldsmobile Convertible (1954). 11. Cunningham Convertible (1953).
    - Morang Robinson Auto Co. - Saperstone, Mr. B. (Box 5, Folder 4)
      Purchases of the following autos: 1. Ford Pickup (1948). 2. Ford Pickup (1952). 3. Ford Country Squire (1955). 4. Ford Express Truck (1955). 5. Packard (1938). 6. Lincoln Cosmopolitan Convertible (1948). 7. Mercury Station Wagon (1950). 8. Chrysler Crown Imperial (1952).
    - Steuart, L. Pine - Williams, H. M., Inc. (Box 5, Folder 5)
      Purchases of the following autos: 1. Jeep (1947). 2. Ford Station Wagon (1938). 3. Lincoln Continental Cabriolet (1940). 4. Ford Thunderbird (1955). 5. Ford Pickup (1948). 6. Ford Convertible (1954). 7. Ford Pickup (1958). 8. Studebaker Champion Regal Deluxe (1947).
  - Jewelry, 2.5
    - Cartier, Inc. - Fiato, Paul E. (Box 5, Folder 1)
      Jewelry purchases presented to: 1. The Children. 2. Mary C. Rockefeller. 3. Mrs. Pierson D. Briggs. 4. Mrs. NAR.
    - Rubel, John Co. - Schlumberger, Inc. (Box 5, Folder 2)
      Jewelry purchases presented to: 1. Mary C. Rockefeller. 2. NAR (himself). 3. Mrs. NAR. 4. Abby R. Pandel. 5. Steven C. Rockefeller
    - Schlumberger, Inc. - Yard, Raymond C. Inc. (Box 5, Folder 3)
      Jewelry purchases presented to: 1. Mary C. Rockefeller. 2. Michael Rockefeller. 3. Mary Rockefeller. 4. Mrs. NAR. 5. Mrs. Rodman Rockefeller. 6. Mrs. JDR Jr. 7. Barbara Olsen.
  - Film, 2.6
    - Guffanti Film Laboratories - Walt Disney Productions (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Taxes, 2.7
    Conditions Governing Access
    Restricted - pending archival review
    - Dacor - Wright (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Banks, 2.8
    - Chase Manhattan Bank, 1955 July-1956 June (Box 6, Folder 1)
      Categories of purchases include: 1. Notes and Mortgages. 2. Art. 3. Personal. 4. Venezuela. 5. Securities. 6. Real Estate
    - Chase Manhattan Bank, 1956 June-1957 February (Box 6, Folder 2)
      Categories of purchases include: 1. Art. 2. Peronal. 3. Real Estate. 4. Securities.
    - Chase Manhattan Bank, 1957 March-1958 February (Box 6, Folder 3)
      Categories of purchases include: 1. Art. 2. Furnishings. 3. Personal.
    - Chase Manhattan Bank, 1958 February-April (Box 6, Folder 4)
      Categories of purchases include: 1. Art. 2. Personal. 3. Notes Payable.
    - Chase Manhattan Bank, 1958 April-September (Box 6, Folder 5)
      Categories of purchases include: 1. Art. 2. Personal. 3. Notes Payable. 4. Real Estate
    - Chase National Bank, 1937 March-1954 March (Box 6, Folder 6)
      Categories of purchases include: 1. Furnishings. 2. Art. 3. Real Estate. 4. Chirgua Farm. 5. Venezuela.
    - Chase National Bank, 1954 April-1955 September (Box 6, Folder 7)
      Categories of purchases include: 1. Art. 2. Venezeula, 3. Notes and Mortgages. 4. Personal.
    - First National City Bank of New York - National City Bank (City Bank Farmers Branch), 1952 April-1956 February (Box 6, Folder 8)
      Categories of purchases include: 1. Personal. 2. Art. 3. Chirgua Farm.
    - Cash, 1935 December-1956 June (Box 6, Folder 9)
      Categories of purchases include: 1. Personal. 2. Auto and Assets. 3. Art. 4. Notes Receivable.
  - Securities, 2.9
    - Allied Bronze Corp. - Barr, Irons & Lane, Inc., 1934 April-1952 March (Box 7, Folder 1)
      Work done at the following properties: 1. Pocantico Hills (Guest House). 2. 13 West 54th Street, NYC. 3. 810 Fifth Avenue, NYC.
    - Barr & Lane, Inc., 1938 July-1939 January (Box 7, Folder 2)
      Work done at the following properties: 810 Fifth Avenue, NYC.
    - Bobbink & Atkins - Cox Kitchens, Inc., 1937 September-1956 September (Box 7, Folder 3)
      Work done at the following properties: 1. Pocantico Hills (Guest House). 2. 810 Fifth Avenue, NYC. 3. Pocantico Hills Maintenance.
    - Dalquist Manufacturing Co., Inc. - Gasperini Construction Corp., 1938 September-1956 October (Box 7, Folder 4)
      Work done at the following properties: Pocantico Hills (Guest House). 810 Fifth Avenue, NYC. Pocantico Hills Maintenance.
    - I. Gaynor Inc. - Kilham, Jeanette, 1934 November-1957 September (Box 7, Folder 5)
      Work done at the following properties: 811 Fifth Avenue, NYC. Pocantico Hills Guest House and maintenance.
    - Kilham, Peter - King, James & Sons, Inc., 1934 November-1948 November (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - King, James & Sons, Inc., 1948 February-July (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - King, James & Sons, Inc., 1951 September 11 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - King, James & Sons, Inc., 1952 March (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Knoll Associates, Inc., 1946 December-1951 February (Box 8, Folder 10)
      Work done at the following properties: 1. 56th Floor Office. 2. 810 Fifth Avenue, NYC. 3. 811 Fifth Avenue, NYC.
    - Knoll Associates, Inc. - Lord & Burnham Company, 1938 September-1957 March (Box 8, Folder 11)
      Work done at the following properties: 1. 22 West 55th Street. 2. 810 Fifth Avenue. 3. Pocantico Hills (Guest House).
    - Margotta Construction Company, Inc., 1947 May-1948 October (Box 8, Folder 12)
      Work done at the following properties: Pocantico Hills maintenance
    - Margotta Construction Company, Inc. - Mosher & Dunagan, Inc., 1939 January-1952 February (Box 9, Folder 13)
      Work done at the following properties: 1. Pocantico Hills maintenance. 2. 146 Union Avenue, Tarrytown, NY. 3. Pocantico Hills (Guest House).
    - Murphy Brinkworth Construction Corp., 1937 April-1939 May (Box 9, Folder 14)
      Work done at the following properties: 1. 810 Fifth Avenue. 2. Pocantico Hills (Guest House).
    - Murphy Brinkworth Construction Corp., 1939 June-1950 August (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Murphy Brinkworth Construction Corp., 1952 April-1957 May (Box 9, Folder 16)
      Work done at the following properties: 1. 13 West 54th Street, NYC. 2. 810 Fifth Avenue, NYC.
    - New York Woodworking Corp. - Universal Sheet Metal Corp., 1938 October-1952 September (Box 9, Folder 17)
      Work done at the following properties: 810 Fifth Avenue and 811 Fifth Avenue, NYC. 51st Floor Office, NYC. Pocantico Hills Guest House and maintenance.
    - Rudolf Wendel, Inc., 1935 April-1957 August (Box 9, Folder 18)
      Work done at the following properties: 810 Fifth Avenue and 811 Fifth Avenue, NYC. 13 West 54th Street, NYC. 2500 Foxhall Road, Washington, DC.
    - Westchester Lighting Co. - Whiffen Electric Co. Inc., 1938 December-1947 June (Box 9, Folder 19)
      Work done at the following properties: Pocantico Hills Guest House and maintenance
  - Real Estate, 2.10
    - Abberley Bride Kooiman McFall and Amon - Battista, Albert D. & Son, 1946 October-1958 August (Box 10, Folder 1)
      Vouchers related to the following property - 1. 9 East 62nd Street, 2. Ranch in Texas, 3. Art Gallery, Seal Harbor, ME 4. 13 West 54th Street, NYC. 5. 27 West 53rd Street, NYC. 6. 146 Union Avenue, Tarrytown, NY 7. 2500 Foxhall Road, Washington DC
    - Berall-Jasper Fence Co. - Burrows, Francis H., 1947 April-1958 February (Box 10, Folder 2)
      Vouchers related to the following property - 1. 2500 Foxhall Road, Washington DC. 2. Seal Harbor, ME. 3. Art Gallery, Seal Harbor, ME.
    - Carper, J. H. - Combustioner Corp., 1947 December-1957 May (Box 10, Folder 3)
      Vouchers related to the following property - 1. 2500 Foxhall Road, Washington DC. 2. 22 West 55th Street, NYC. 3. 2412 Foxhall Road, Washington, DC.
    - Conary, Henry - Damon, Waldo, Jr., 1945 December-1958 January (Box 10, Folder 4)
      Vouchers related to the following property - 1. Seal Harbor, ME. 2. 15 West 54th Street, NYC. 3. Chirgua Farm. 4. 2500 Foxhall Road, Washington, DC.
    - Debevoise, Plimpton & McLean - Derevere, Frederick M., 1957 May-1958 August (Box 10, Folder 5)
      Vouchers related to the following property - 1. Beach property in Sardinia. 2. Seal Harbor, ME.
    - Durand Taylor Co. - Heckinger Engineering Corp., 1937 October-1957 August (Box 10, Folder 6)
      Vouchers related to the following property - Seal Harbor, ME. 2500 Foxhall Road, Washington DC. Sutton Island, ME. 13 West 54th Street, and other properties.
    - The Hills Realty Co. - Jaffe, 1953 March-1957 July (Box 10, Folder 7)
      Vouchers related to the following property - 1. Pocantico Hills. 2. Santa Rita Farm, Brazil. 3. Art Gallery, Seal Harbor, ME. 4. Seal Harbor, ME. 5. 2500 Foxhall Road, Washington DC.
    - Johnson, Philip, Assoc. - Jordan, Everett G. Inc., 1947 October-1958 July (Box 11, Folder 8)
      Vouchers related to the following property - Seal Harbor, ME including Art Gallery
    - Kirkland, L. A. - Lord Electric Co., Inc., 1939 March-1958 January (Box 11, Folder 9)
      Vouchers related to the following property - Ranch in Texas. Seal Harbor, ME. "The Park", Pocantico Hills, NY. 13 West 54th Street, NYC.
    - Lynch, Bernard - McCann, E. S., 1950 November-1957 July (Box 11, Folder 10)
      Vouchers related to the following property - Seal Harbor, ME. 2500 Foxhall Road, Washington DC. 20 West 55th Street, NYC, 13 West 54th Street, NYC
    - Wm. P. Lipscomb Co., Inc. (Box 11, Folder 11)
      Vouchers related to the following property - 2500 Foxhall Road, Washington, DC
    - Wm. P. Lipscomb Co., Inc. (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - McGilynn Associates, Inc. - Milbank, Tweed, Hope & Hadley, 1936 December-1958 September (Box 11, Folder 13)
      Vouchers related to the following property - 1. 20 West 55th Street, NYC. 2. 13 West 54th Street, NYC. 3. 810 Fifth Avenue. 4. 2500 Foxhall Road, Washington DC. 5. 15 West 54th Street, NYC.
    - Milbank, Tweed, Hope & Hadley - Nelson, Gustav E., 1938 October-1958 August (Box 11, Folder 14)
      Vouchers related to the following property - 1. 2500 Foxhall Road, Washington DC. 2. Seal Harbor, ME. 3. 146 Union Avenue, Tarrytown, NY.
    - Norwood, L. E. - Reed, Washington, Jr., 1939 June-1957 September (Box 12, Folder 15)
      Vouchers related to the following property - Seal Harbor, ME. Pocantico Hills, NY. 13 West 54th Street, NYC. 22 West 55th Street, NYC, Shingle Island, ME, and other properties.
    - Schaefer, Chas - Simpson, Edwin K., 1939 July-1958 March (Box 12, Folder 16)
      Vouchers related to the following property - 13 West 54th Street, NYC, Pocantico Hills, NY, 22 West 55 Street, NYC, Tarrytown Crest House, NY, Seal Harbor, ME, Shingle Island, ME and other properties.
    - Sinclair Refining Co. - J. H. Small & Sons, 1945 July-1957 October (Box 12, Folder 17)
      Vouchers related to the following property - 1. 2500 Foxhall Road, Washington DC. 2. Art Gallery, Seal Harbor, ME.
    - J. H. Small & Sons, 1954 March-1956 February (Box 12, Folder 18)
      Vouchers related to the following property - 2500 Foxhall Road, Washington DC. 2.
    - Smallidge, C. M. - Stanley, Woodbury A., 1939 July-1958 September (Box 12, Folder 19)
      Vouchers related to the following property - 1. Seal Harbor, ME. 2. 13 West 54th Street, NYC. 3. 20 West 54th Street, NYC
    - Stanley, Woodbury A. - Trunnel, W. K., 1949 October-1958 January (Box 12, Folder 20)
      Vouchers related to the following property - Seal Harbor, ME. 810 Fifth Avenue, NYC. 22 West 55th Street, NYC. 811 Fifth Avenue Corp., 20 West 55th Street, NYC. 2500 Foxhall Road, Washington, DC.
    - Venetian Blind Refinishing Co. - Wheelwright, Mary, 1935 July-1957 September (Box 12, Folder 21)
      Vouchers related to the following property - 1. Chirgua Farm. 2. Hacienda Palo Gordo. 3. Art Gallery, ME.
    - White, R. L., 1940 July-1941 September (Box 12, Folder 22)
      Vouchers related to the following property - 1. Shingle Island, ME. 2. Seal Harbor, ME. 3. Pyle Property, ME.
    - White, R. L., 1941 October-1942 February (Box 13, Folder 23)
      Vouchers related to the following property - Seal Harbor, ME.
    - White, R. L., 1942 March-June (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - White, R. L., 1942 July-September (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - White, R. L., 1942 December-1947 March (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - White, R. L., 1946 December-1951 October (Box 13, Folder 27)
      Vouchers related to the following property - 1. Seal Harbor, ME. 2. Pocantico Hills, NY.
    - White, Wm. A. & Sons - Yates, William, 1952 August-1956 September (Box 13, Folder 28)
      Vouchers related to the following property - 1. 27 West 53rd Street. 2. 2500 Foxhall Road, Washington, DC. 3. "The Park", Pocantico Hills, NY.
  - Art, 2.11
    - The Allan Gallery, Inc. - Bennett, Rainey, 1937 March-1958 October (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Bigelow, Priscilla - Boston Truck Co., Inc., 1956 July-1958 July (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Bucholz Gallery, 1939 March-1951 July (Box 14, Folder 3)
      Voucher 10515 Pablo Picasso's "La Mandoliniste" (1910) purchased in 1950 for 7,956 dollars.
    - Budworth, W. S. & Son. Inc. - Carlebach Gallery, 1949 March-1950 December (Box 14, Folder 4)
      Much of the art purchased from Carlebach Gallery is Indian and folk art (African, etc.)
    - Carlebach Gallery, 1951 February-1952 November (Box 14, Folder 5)